{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272129959","data":{"timestamp":" 947272129959"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272173851","data":{"timestamp":" 947272173851"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272173915","data":{"timestamp":" 947272173915"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" e30ed5b4-49a4-489d-94ad-acb2fba922df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKIMA"," userResponse":" SAKIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272181184","data":{"timestamp":" 947272181184"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" e30ed5b4-49a4-489d-94ad-acb2fba922df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272188933","data":{"timestamp":" 947272188933"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" e30ed5b4-49a4-489d-94ad-acb2fba922df"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini Sakima alikuwa mvulana mwenye talanta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272197452","data":{"timestamp":" 947272197452"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272199587","data":{"timestamp":" 947272199586"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272201726","data":{"timestamp":" 947272201726"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272204922","data":{"timestamp":" 947272204922"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272207201","data":{"timestamp":" 947272207200"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272209493","data":{"timestamp":" 947272209492"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272212320","data":{"timestamp":" 947272212320"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272214544","data":{"timestamp":" 947272214543"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272216767","data":{"timestamp":" 947272216766"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272220046","data":{"timestamp":" 947272220045"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272222169","data":{"timestamp":" 947272222169"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272224302","data":{"timestamp":" 947272224301"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272227294","data":{"timestamp":" 947272227293"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272229556","data":{"timestamp":" 947272229556"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272231818","data":{"timestamp":" 947272231818"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272234855","data":{"timestamp":" 947272234855"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272237209","data":{"timestamp":" 947272237208"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272239600","data":{"timestamp":" 947272239599"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272242654","data":{"timestamp":" 947272242654"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272244827","data":{"timestamp":" 947272244827"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272246963","data":{"timestamp":" 947272246962"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272250155","data":{"timestamp":" 947272250154"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272252340","data":{"timestamp":" 947272252340"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272254522","data":{"timestamp":" 947272254522"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272257735","data":{"timestamp":" 947272257734"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272260127","data":{"timestamp":" 947272260126"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272262565","data":{"timestamp":" 947272262565"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272265707","data":{"timestamp":" 947272265707"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272267990","data":{"timestamp":" 947272267990"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272270214","data":{"timestamp":" 947272270214"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272273187","data":{"timestamp":" 947272273187"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272275429","data":{"timestamp":" 947272275429"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272277669","data":{"timestamp":" 947272277668"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272280643","data":{"timestamp":" 947272280642"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272283001","data":{"timestamp":" 947272283001"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272285355","data":{"timestamp":" 947272285354"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272288543","data":{"timestamp":" 947272288542"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272290947","data":{"timestamp":" 947272290946"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272293318","data":{"timestamp":" 947272293318"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272296300","data":{"timestamp":" 947272296299"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272298589","data":{"timestamp":" 947272298589"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272300872","data":{"timestamp":" 947272300872"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272304104","data":{"timestamp":" 947272304103"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272306359","data":{"timestamp":" 947272306358"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272308665","data":{"timestamp":" 947272308664"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272312060","data":{"timestamp":" 947272312059"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272314537","data":{"timestamp":" 947272314536"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272317014","data":{"timestamp":" 947272317014"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272319929","data":{"timestamp":" 947272319929"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272322139","data":{"timestamp":" 947272322138"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272324368","data":{"timestamp":" 947272324367"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272327793","data":{"timestamp":" 947272327792"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272330140","data":{"timestamp":" 947272330139"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272332492","data":{"timestamp":" 947272332492"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272335518","data":{"timestamp":" 947272335518"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272337752","data":{"timestamp":" 947272337752"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272340041","data":{"timestamp":" 947272340040"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272343114","data":{"timestamp":" 947272343114"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272345270","data":{"timestamp":" 947272345270"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272347415","data":{"timestamp":" 947272347415"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272350560","data":{"timestamp":" 947272350559"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272352821","data":{"timestamp":" 947272352821"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272355076","data":{"timestamp":" 947272355075"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272358294","data":{"timestamp":" 947272358293"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272360492","data":{"timestamp":" 947272360492"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272362715","data":{"timestamp":" 947272362715"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272365899","data":{"timestamp":" 947272365899"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272368177","data":{"timestamp":" 947272368176"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272370511","data":{"timestamp":" 947272370510"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272373694","data":{"timestamp":" 947272373693"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272376068","data":{"timestamp":" 947272376067"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272378413","data":{"timestamp":" 947272378413"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272381820","data":{"timestamp":" 947272381819"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272381936","data":{"timestamp":" 947272381936"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_50","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272388981","data":{"timestamp":" 947272388981"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" d5f9686d-31ec-4222-a911-770a850a1a13"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272401338","data":{"timestamp":" 947272401337"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272404123","data":{"timestamp":" 947272404123"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JASHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272405748","data":{"timestamp":" 947272405748"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272408260","data":{"timestamp":" 947272408260"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIWE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272409898","data":{"timestamp":" 947272409897"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272412263","data":{"timestamp":" 947272412262"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272413865","data":{"timestamp":" 947272413864"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272416426","data":{"timestamp":" 947272416426"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JICHO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272418046","data":{"timestamp":" 947272418045"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272420561","data":{"timestamp":" 947272420561"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272422183","data":{"timestamp":" 947272422182"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEKUNDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272425286","data":{"timestamp":" 947272425285"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEKUNDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272426889","data":{"timestamp":" 947272426888"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272432861","data":{"timestamp":" 947272432860"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272434498","data":{"timestamp":" 947272434497"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272436838","data":{"timestamp":" 947272436838"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JEMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272438452","data":{"timestamp":" 947272438452"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272441113","data":{"timestamp":" 947272441113"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272443130","data":{"timestamp":" 947272443129"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272443244","data":{"timestamp":" 947272443244"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272459663","data":{"timestamp":" 947272459662"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:J..J.all.rand.all.stat.show.45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272465575","data":{"timestamp":" 947272465575"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272551866","data":{"timestamp":" 947272551865"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" 6349413a-f129-481a-81ef-ccf2c88b91cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" JIKONI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947272551959","data":{"timestamp":" 947272551959"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_220835"," gameId":" a2e473a8-cc01-4fba-8f57-ff4376e0418a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_47"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa mfano aliweza kuketi na watu wazima na kujadili mambo ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" MUHIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}